

Sahand Edrisian

(916) 804-1935 me@1sahand.com Sacramento, CA

Profile

I'm a fifteen year old, one of Apple's WWDC 2015 scholarship winners! I'm a professional iOS developer currently working at Musey. I started programming from the age of 10, so i have lots of experience. I do lots of different stuff, from making apps for the Apple Watch to programming Designing PCB boards for my robot. I like working remotely.

Experience

IOS DEVELOPER AT MUSEY INC. - 2015 - PRESENT

I currently work at Musey a San Fransisco based company. I work on their iOS Apps. And also manage their backend services such as Parse. I am legally working with a work permit. You can download our app <u>Scout</u> on the App Store.

SELF EMPLOYED IOS DEVELOPER – 2013-2015

I have lots of iOS knowledge. I started with Objective-C and learnt Swift as soon as it was out. I love making iOS Apps. I have 5 Apps on the app store.

SELF EMPLOYED .NET AND WEB DEVELOPER – 2010-2013

I started programming from the age of 10. I started with C#, making windows apps. I also sold an accounting app i made to a company. I like web development too. I make my own REST apis.

Education

Rio Americano High School – Currently a Sophomore

Skills

iOS Development, Swift, Apple Watch, Objective-C, game development.

C#, .NET, Web Development, Node.js, PHP, MYSQL, Parse.

Links

<u>Facebook</u> <u>Twitter</u> <u>My Website</u> <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Github</u> <u>My Apps</u>